Apart from this, after the market closed yesterday, let us
also take a look at the results and news that came in.
Sharad has joined us
with the details. Sharad D. Good morning.
First of all, tell me how the results came in and
after that, tell us about the news. And
what will be the figures for today, please share that with you. Yes,
absolutely. Good morning, Pooja. So,
first of all, let us focus on earnings. And
tomorrow, after the market today, the results of ICC Lombard
General Insurance will come. If we look at the
overall results, they will be mixed because
in tax learning, the numbers were slightly lower than expected.
But if we look at the overall revenue
and their important parameters, the
updates that came in for an insurance company have been overall in line. Net
premium returned increased by 2% on air basis. And as far as the
thing is, there has been an increase of 40% here. The second
stock will be Tata Coffee. Now, here we have
seen mixed results, but due to the
increase in product realization, there has been a
10% increase in revenue.
And of course, there has been a change in product
mix. And in the markets of India and Vietnam
also  Good performance has been
seen, there has been an increase of about 9%,
however, there is
still some pressure on the operating profit. There was a
decline of 240 basis points on the basis of Bida Mars, so
this can be an overall mix
set of earnings. You have seen both Tata Coffee and
ICC Lombard General Insurance,
but we will keep some triggers on G today.
In the fourth Mike's result,
three companies are going up, ICC Security
Master and Tata Communications. Sir, yesterday we were
also seeing ceiling pressure. I have
expected that there is some deceleration in the market,
especially in Tata Communications
and ICC Securities, we may
see lower numbers because the
trading volumes have now reduced, as was
seen in the first quarter of 2023. BML's land
assets are going to be listed and this
script is coming in your TT segment,
now remember in the tractor trade segment,
which is land assets and when  When the stock was
completed in the month of September,
its value was around ₹362 per share and now the
value given by Antique Broking House is
around 624% of the asset, so
you should definitely keep it under focus. Apart from this, you should
keep your focus on the news stocks in the
farmers space. Two important news is coming
in the Parallel Pharma stock. There has been significant
betting since the demerger
from Parmal Enterprises. But now a positive
news has definitely come that the FDA
inspection has been completed. The
inspection report has been
issued for that facility but not a
single observation has been noticed. So,
a kind of positive reaction can be seen in the stock.
In Jidest Life Sciences
also, Usavada's final approval has been given for the
bone treatment drug, so
you should definitely keep a focus on this as well, but important deal
specific movements are also being
seen. Yesterday, there was 16 wine or
their recently listed in the month of December.  The
shareholding pattern has been updated here.
This investor Mukul Agarwal has
increased his stake from 1.9% to 2.38%.
Aplat Technologies was listed yesterday
and after the listing, an important block
deal took place where Goldman Sachs bought
about 8 lakh shares. The
capital raising program of the bank which is being done
with the sale for 2014 is also
focused on. Here SBI will raise two billion
dollars from foreign investment. On the other hand, if
you talk about Bank of India,
they will also have a capital raising program of Rs 6500 crore and
both security and debt components will be included in it.
Somdistris is also going to be in focus
and here the expanded capacity of the company in
Karnataka has now
started commercial production. Now remember that the
summer season is also coming and the
production and consumption of beer is at
peak levels, so a
positive reaction can be seen in this type of stock.
Ped Light Industries is
that base company of the agreement.  Based on an aid, where the
assets are going to be transferred technically,
but now management changes are also being
seen. Here General Stainless has made a
real point. Now Hriday Jindal, who is going to be in
HD for the next five years, has been appointed as the CEO of Bajaj
Healthcare. Sajjan Kumar Bajaj, who is a
Chamar and HD, has been appointed.
And in Lux also, Kapil Jain from
UK has been made the CEO. He has
almost two decades of experience in Infosys
in the BPM segment. The last stock will be in
Fox, Ratan India Enterprises.
Here they have started the D2C fashion brand
business
with a new brand. But one more development has
come. Tomorrow, Tata Power will be in Fox.
Here, Cric has directed
their Mundra plant to
generate power provisions on the basis of area 11.
What used to happen earlier was that the
temporary
outstanding payments of the power of the Mundra unit have been taken, but in a kind of
sentimentally positive news, you can
see Tata Power, so
keep an eye on it and we will also see some results.  I have
come to Zee that today we can see the reaction,
thank you for giving all this information.